Hey,
Hello, hello.
Hello, everyone.
Nice to see everyone here today.
Hi.
Danny, good to see you.
Nancy, Don, Pablo, Mike.
Thanks for joining, Mike.
be here.
Um, okay, cool.
So we can kind of dot, maybe some, some
people will join here obviously midori will
keep it open but we have a, we have an
intimate setting here, so we can kind of,
um, of course take personal questions,
kind of unpack things a little bit with
whatever's going on in your situation.
Of course.
Um, I did want to take a quick minute, um,
to
just sort of remind you all one quick thing
that we kind of unpacked on the last
session, just to sort of bring everything
back.
So we say this throughout the program a
lot.
We emphasize it a lot at the beginning.
And as we go through, we certainly tell
you to focus on one thing, right?
You're going to do these assessments,
understand what good looks like in your
business, but in working with Claude, it's
also going to point your highest leverage
opportunity that's going to be tied to your
strategic initiatives, right?
And in the last session, I believe it was
Montgomery, he talked about, hey, I'm
starting to get a little bit overwhelmed.
And typically what we have seen to be
true is that happens because as you do go
through these things, our brains are just
sort of wired to start seeing what's
possible.
And then, so, for example, it might play
out, like I do an assessment and I did it for
marketing and now I see what good looks
like.
And now I want to start implementing for
marketing.
And then I do that with operations.
And then I do that with sales.
And then I kind of rinse and repeat.
And so I just want to pull everyone back to
remind you is that is not the best practice
and not actually what you want to do
during the cohort.
Because if you do that, you're pretty much
guaranteed to get very overwhelmed very,
very quickly.
And then also your quality of output on all
of the things that you try to start
implementing will not be at the level that
they could or should.
So again, we don't want to scale chaos.
We want to make sure that we're doing
the assessments.
We're seeing what good looks like, you
know, four levels deep in everybody's
business.
And then when we get to implementation,
you know, relative to the size of your
team, we'll focus on that more towards
the latter of the cohort, which is really
what the last few sessions are about.
So, hey, all of you have a one thing or
perhaps you're a mature organization and
you have a team and we're going to talk
all about
what that's going to look like when we get
to that point.
So with that said, we did talk, you know,
sales and offer excellence on Monday's
session.
And so perhaps it's good.
I know we had kind of two points of how
we were looking at that for solopreneurs
and smaller teams, or maybe people who
don't have sales teams.
I've put both things you all requested
inside circle.
So I took a Loom video showing you
essentially things that I've done from a
fractional sales management standpoint
for managing multiple teams.
And essentially that was using Cloud for
speed, efficiency, quality of output, and
just a multiplier of my time.
And I gave you some examples there.
And then I also shared the example of an
actual workflow that we have in another
one of Hayden's businesses that is
completely automated.
So the key with those things
just like all of the things in this course,
because all of you run different types of
businesses.
But a big key is just to understand what's
possible, right?
Because for clarity, you know, a lot of that
might have sounded a very high level and
perhaps too technical for anybody on this
call, but really the only starting point to
do any of the workflows that we went
over is going to be the transcription of a
call.
And everyone has the ability, whether
you're on a phone call or you're on a Zoom
or Google Meet or any type of video
conferencing call to be able to transcribe a
call.
And that's the only action that causes the
rest of that campaign.
And it does not have to just be for sales.
This could be for things like onboarding,
your client success, things like account
managers.
It really, really could be spread across
other areas of your business too.
Wanted to quickly just go over those
things on the overwhelm and then circle
back.
But if anybody has been doing the lead to
sale assessment, trying to, you know,
evaluate your sales process and
optimization, any of those things, I mean,
we can open it up there.
Or of course, if you all have specific
questions, we're happy to go over.
I feel a bit with bad conscious when I come
to the office hour because I'm quite
behind.
So I partially met the assessments in the
past from UVP on and still I was very
overwhelmed like you mentioned now
how Montgomery said it and for me This is
really key transcribing.
And I told this colleague today and he is
sales guy.
So goes for physical goods to B2B
customers.
So dealer.
And I told him and he said then, hey, but I
need to have a consent if I record my
talks.
So if I go for lunch, for instance, and I
place my iPhone to the table, I need
confirmation that it is okay.
It's not the same if you do it with virtual
calls and then you see it with a red dot or
something like that, that it is recorded.
This is just the thinking after the session
you gave input.
But this...
made me also a bit frustrated, let's say, so
that I'm not sure I can really achieve this
fundamental.
Okay.
Well, let me try to answer both things that
you mentioned.
So the first thing about being
overwhelmed, just remove that pressure,
Benny.
Yes.
You know, again, so If this is helpful, all of
you are different, right?
One thing that you all have in common is
you're running a business while you're
doing this cohort.
And I will quickly, I think I've shared this,
but we've tested different timelines of
delivery.
And so we've tried to find a balance,
getting feedback from people like
yourselves, of course, of saying like, hey,
there's all types of courses people take,
whether they're, you can do this, you have
access to it for a year or six months or
whatever that looks like.
And also saying, What's the fastest
amount of time that you could come into
this cohort and actually have a, an
operating system built that's going to
provide transformation in just a few
weeks.
And so that's kind of where we are in like
this six week timeline.
So for you or anybody, uh, being
overwhelmed with what I opened about,
like you're not focused on executing
anything.
You're not focused on when you see a plan
of implementation to tell a team member
start building.
start doing these things.
So for you, I mean, of course, look at your
time, right?
You, you have been on all these sessions.
Each of these sessions is about an hour.
That's about an hour.
Let's call it an hour and a half a week.
And then everything that you're going to
be doing with the assessments, right?
You are providing deep thought.
And if you're doing that appropriately, it
does take a little bit of time.
Um, with that said, most of the people
that I've asked in doing it that way,
can plan for anywhere between 7 to 10
hours a week.
And so for you, just think of that the best
that you can.
Of course, all of these are recorded, but
we appreciate you showing up.
In terms of the recording, I think we
actually talked about this on the last
session.
So we do recordings.
The easy part, to your point, on any video
conferencing, when you all just joined, it
says this is the very first thing.
this session is being recorded.
And that is for the exact legal issues of if
you are recording a call, you do have to let
people know.
Now, I've done this on phone calls in a
variety of different ways from outbound
calls to people who immediately opt into
an ad that a setter calls, or you have
people that are on your list that you are
calling, not cold because they're on your
list, but cold in the sense they're out of
the blue.
Like, hey, it's just Josh giving you a call to
talk about And in doing that after maybe
you're open, if it's a cold outbound call,
um, you just say you, you, I have them
part of like a script.
If, if you have like scripts, I have them say
that just so you know, this call is being
recorded for training purposes.
So it's, you do have to do that, uh, for
anybody who communicates to people
and you're going to do something with
that recording, you do have to
communicate to the prospect and or
customer that you're speaking to.
I would, I would add improvement
purposes.
Yeah.
And also it's literally what we're talking
about, right?
Cause you're, you're saying you, you sort
of presented the workflow.
So any, anytime you're going to take call
notes, um, that's why the language I like is
for training purposes, because it actually
is for training purposes.
We're going to take that information.
In our workflow, there are no admin tasks
anymore.
There's no salesperson taking notes.
That is immediately taken from bubbles in
our case, but Otter or whatever software
you all use to record your calls, there's
probably a thousand of them out there
right now.
And so that is the start of a very, very
simple workflow, even at a one-off level.
If you just took your call notes and you
automated that into your CRM, That alone
would save, I can tell you as someone
who's managed reps, that will save them a
ton of time for them to focus more on
selling.
So, Nancy, I'll get to you second.
I think Don has had his hand up.
Just wanted to make a comment for
Benny, because I also, everything you just
said about starting with a transcription
and I'm not satisfied with my system, but
what I've been doing in individual
one-on-one meetings with staff,
is I just say, okay, I'm going to give
ChatGBT the following prompt.
I'm going to make a series of recordings.
Don't do anything at the end until I tell
you to summarize.
And I tell the person I'm doing that.
And then I pay attention because I have
to, like you can do 10 minutes and just
keep on recording.
And then I share with them what the
summary was of the meeting, which has
been appreciated on both sides by, that's
not the final solution, but maybe with the
salespeople, you let them know and the
other person can confirm it, you know,
just confirm that this is everything that
we did.
That's worked.
you know, I'm not, it's not the final
solution, but it's worked quite well.
People have responded.
Those are internally, but appreciated
getting the same thing that I'm looking at
as our summary.
Anyway.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Hopefully that's helpful, Benny.
And by the way, Nancy, I, I, I sort of gave
examples of how you could use cloud in
projects.
So I've done very similar things when I
drop end of days or end of week reports.
I will have, when I've managed like remote
sales teams, I will do,
you know, daily meetings, proper tracking
and end of day reporting.
And all of that feeds into real time
coaching.
And I, if you do it at the project level, AI is
not replacing you by any means.
It's just a multiplier for you.
So you still use your judgment, but you're
able to use it for all the time consuming
things.
And it's, it's literally endless relative to
your sales process or again, your
operations.
I know before I get to you, Don, another
quick example.
is I ran a digital agency for years.
And so what we determined on delivery to
success was that the most important call
was our onboarding call.
If our onboarding call was a home run
with a new client, the odds of that person
staying with us and retaining was almost
99%.
And so we had to take a few iterations of
what a great onboarding call looked like,
but then we had that
And then in this example, let's say if it
were five things, you know, Benny, you're
in medical device, so I'm sure there's a lot
of specific things that you might need to
cover.
Well, then you have that as a framework,
a script or sales process overview or
onboarding really again, removing what it
is.
It's just a framework.
And then with the notes, it would flag like,
well, one of the main five things was not
covered on this call.
And so it starts to give a real time
feedback loop.
to alert you as the owner, manager, et
cetera, to then go back to the rep.
You're doing daily meetings, you're doing
one-to-ones, and you're doing all the
things that you need to do, whether it be
for sales or delivery, if helpful.
Don.
Hello, everybody.
Thanks for all this stuff.
I think the most important thing I want to
ask you about, Josh, is in the world of...
the sales training, okay?
So you have the recording of the call
happening, the AI summary, the checklist,
and so on.
And then somewhere along the way, you
really turn on my lights when it's like,
yeah, and how about weighing that
against a standard and pointing out to
everybody how that call could be done
better?
Are they checking off the boxes, asking
the questions, letting the customer talk?
most of the time.
And I was just wondering if you have any
experience with that and if you want to
comment on what you've learned from
observing that happening, maybe.
Yeah, and so my answer is it's no different
than what you're doing with your master
prompt.
So even at the project level, Don, and
again, like if you want to automate a
workflow, that's a little bit different.
But I'll just say if you wanted to build a
project to deliver any type of outcome,
to get feedback on whatever.
You really want to give it context, right?
Before you all doing this, if you went to
ChatGPT or Claude or Gronk or Gemini,
any LLM, and you said, give me a go-to
market strategy for my company.
It would give you an answer, but it would
be kind of no different than like a Google
search, right?
Because it doesn't have context.
And so when I'm building anything, so let's
say a call review, And you can do that
where you can automate all the calls to go
in.
I basically would build as many project
files for context as possible.
And so that could come in the form, just
ideas of like a script, like, Hey, this is the
script, especially if your call is meant to be
done in the same type of way, the same
type of flow every single time, of course,
in a lot of calls, there's a lot of nuance to
sales, but, um, there's, um, a script, uh,
a list of how you handle specific
objections.
One thing that all of us will deal with,
regardless of B2B, B2C, we all deal with
the same objections in sales.
All of us.
It's the exact same ones.
It doesn't matter what you do in business.
And so listing how your company
specifically handles those to make sure
that the rep is doing that very well.
And the easiest way, once you know what
good looks like for calls specifically is to
dump transcripts of at least 10.
I mean, if you have, I mean, I've worked
with companies that have 2000 sales calls.
You can dump in as many, this is what a
great call looks like transcripts and just
doing something like that.
In the example that I showed you in loom,
if you just drop a transcript to say, grade
this to my sales process overview, it will
say they didn't cover.
this in discovery.
When the objection on money or partner
spouse came up, they didn't handle it like
you internally like to handle.
And so it just makes, again, it's still your
thought leadership, Don, but it's just
saving you a lot of like the time
consuming stuff.
And so the answer is just to build context.
So at another level, salespeople, human
beings have bad habits, right?
oh, you're over-talking.
And so I have been experimenting with
informing AI of high-quality sales training
and then weighing that rather than
working on the script approach.
It's like, are you following the practices
that work best?
And like asking a question and then
shutting up.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
I used to, on this one offer, I used to, I
learned that in sales, to Don's point, if
you're not in the sales world, most people
associate sales with like the gift of gab or
I'm just a good talker, where in reality, the
greatest salespeople, if you look at it like
an audio file, where we see the audio
waves, they ask a question and they talk
about 10% of the time and the other
person talks about 90% of the time.
And so that was something
where you could look at percentages in
that specific case from how much they
speak opposed to the prospect, which is
interesting.
But yeah, look, there's all types of things.
I mean, one thing I solved for salespeople
is a lot of times when salespeople take
their own notes, there's a lot of issues
that come with this.
Some of them are that they won't put
pertinent information.
Right.
They take the call.
They're trying to be present while they're
taking notes on a Google doc or perhaps in
the CRM.
I've done this.
If you've taken sales calls, you've probably
done this.
And then there's a lot of information that
don't make that.
I'll tell you the biggest problem that I've
noticed managing people is that a lot of
salespeople will put in their notes things
that aren't actually true from the call.
If any of you can relate to this, they'll say
something like this person wasn't a good
fit.
And there's a variety of reasons they do
that.
The most common is, is they might want
to just protect their close rate.
So they could say like, oh, this person
wasn't a fit, so I didn't end up pitching
them.
And that would be in their end of day
report.
And then ultimately in the CRM and in the
notes where if you're taking all of the
transcription from the call in the
workflow that we're discussing in any
scenario, in this case sales, um, none of
that can be cloudy.
because everything that happened in that
call is gonna be transcribed and added to
your system as well as next steps.
And then it's going to alert you on
whatever you're measuring good, whether
it's a script, Don, if they spoke too much,
their discovery, if this person was a
qualified lead.
Again, it's about how deep do you wanna
go.
And as long as it has the context, you can
really become unbelievably detailed.
Okay.
So out of respect to people's time, I'm
going to just mention another topic, and
you can decide what you want to do with
it all.
But we did a public works bid last week,
which we didn't win.
We have 10 bid results.
And I took that over to Claude and said,
hey, you know, what can we learn from
this?
And I did a competitor analysis, looked up
each of the 10 bidders, did a total
background on them, and it was really
informative.
So that's informative, right?
Well, I took that over to co-work, Claude
co-work that I just got rolling and said,
hey, give me 10 high priority things I
should do about this.
And I did that.
And the lucidity and the action worthiness
of these 10 ideas that I came up with were
Really exciting.
So wow.
Yeah.
I mean, that's amazing.
Um, if for all of you who don't know about
Claude cowork, by the way, it can start, it
connects on like your local computer.
Uh, it's pretty amazing cause it'll actually,
you know, it's essentially like an AI agent
on your computer.
It'll actually do tasks for you.
So, um, I've used it in a variety of different
ways.
I would use Claude code at this point to
kind of, to kind of do everything myself.
Um, but it, um, you know, for example, if
you have a, bunch of folders on your
desktop.
You're just like, organize my folders,
organize my crazy desktop into three
folders.
It will literally do that.
Uh, sometimes I will have it search
through invoices and find me, pull the
invoices from this folder, uh, over the last
60 days and it will do things like that.
So personal efficiency, it's really, really
cool.
And, um, and yeah, you know, I would,
um, you know, one thing I would add,
cause I'm sure you got a lot of cool stuff
from doing that, Don is I would reach out
to the client
And I would ask them, Hey, I, I, I respect,
you know, the process I just out of
curiosity.
So perhaps we could get better.
What ultimately was the reason that you
chose to go with competitor?
Just so we know.
And, um, that will do a lot for you.
Um, but you know, perhaps it could be
speed, which with proposals and
especially in, in your line of work bidding a
lot of the time, that is a huge, huge
bottleneck, as I mentioned in a, in a real
example on Monday's call.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Happy to help anybody else have any
questions on the last session or anything
else as you're, you're kind of, it's okay.
Uh, whether it's Benny or anybody else
that you're behind, remember it's, it's
your pace.
Um, it's your company, it's your schedule,
right?
So we're here to support you in every way
that we can.
So if it's, if it's sales, great, that's kind of
where we are currently in the
assessments, but wherever you are, if
you're going through things, we're,
happy to kind of unpack anything if
helpful.
I just had a question for Don or anybody
else related to competitor information
you're getting back.
We have some competitors that are
publicly traded, but most of our
competitors are smaller, regional.
And so the data that's available when I try
to get competitor information has not
been very helpful necessarily.
I was wondering if Anybody have any tips
related to that or in your situation, Don,
since you felt it was pretty helpful if those
were companies that had like financial
information available publicly or pricing
or anything like that?
I'd like to speak to that if we have the
space here.
Yeah, go ahead.
One of the things that it did was it
provided the context of the companies
that were on the bid list.
And so
One of them had been acquired by a
national operation.
One of them was 200 miles away from the
job.
And so they had a mobilization factor.
And then it's really good at drilling down
into what they're doing with their
marketing.
Because that's pretty visible for anybody
that's doing any marketing.
And they can distinguish whether they're
doing any paid advertising or how heavy
their website is, what their reviews are
like.
It'll do a terrific analysis of the reviews
that it finds online, whether they're
accredited by any kind of
diamond-certified accreditation service,
where they stand with the Better Business
Bureau.
It also pops up with, oh, they took out a
SBA loan with COVID, and it shows how
much they borrowed it.
which is really weird.
So you can get a lot of background out of
it, and a lot of that stuff just comes
without even asking for it.
It was part of the analysis.
So that's a factor.
I would say that all their advertising is
highly visible.
All right, great.
That was helpful.
I think I ran into some glitches.
I was using the chat when I was doing this
and it didn't, it's having a problem doing
some of the searching.
So it wanted me to do some of the work,
but I've moved to using cowork more
when possible.
Although then you've got to set up the link
to do searches, but I'll just try some of
that again.
Sounds like you got a lot of pretty good
information, even on companies that
aren't public.
Yeah, I fed CoWork the output of the
analysis that Claude Chat gave me.
And I said, what should I do with this?
Give me 10 action items.
And so I never would have come up with
this stuff.
Talk about being overwhelmed, you know.
This completely wiped out the overwhelm
and created this action path that I'm going
to take back to the owner of the company.
How much of this stuff do you want to
execute?
Here's my bill, you know.
because there's a lot of good ideas here,
you know.
And so it also distinguished one of our
strengths that we have on our webpage,
which was that we have 188 FAQs around
our space.
And it says there's no competitor has any
FAQ content.
It's pure SEO territory.
And it said generate some order.
You know, and again, it gave me a list of
things to generate FAQs around.
So that's an example.
It also pointed out some channels of
visibility that we are completely blind to,
you know, that some of our competitors
are actively engaged with.
And so we can go there and, you know,
open up our visibility on those channels,
and that might help, you know.
Thank you for sharing.
Mike, is that helpful?
Yeah, definitely.
One of the things I've realized is
sometimes it's figuring out which tool to
use, especially as you move beyond just
the cloud chat.
It might be interesting to some people,
but I've started using cowork as I
mentioned.
And one of the things, we get a lot of
paper receipts because we have people
running around buying supplies for
different things and we gather those as
we can.
But I set up a skill in cloud to OCR.
So now I'm having my managers scan
directly to Google Drive.
So they all set up an app on their phone,
goes to the same folder.
So instead of scanning paper every week
or two weeks, everything, including the
digital receipts, go directly to the Google
Drive folder, which is synced to desktop.
And then the skill will actually go in there.
We don't have to name the files.
It will OCR everything.
It will
gave it a script to name the file, and then
after all of them are named with date,
accounting code, like put in instructions to
code them, put a job site idea if we
needed, it'll then create an Excel
spreadsheet and put everything in there,
which then is going to save money with
the bookkeepers because everything's so
clean and clear, they can just run through
that really quickly.
they won't even have to open the receipts
and go, okay, what did this guy write?
So I think in the long run that can save a
ton of time.
Yeah.
I will also say, I mean, again, you know, I
don't want, I don't want to go too far
cause obviously you guys are using
cowork.
Um, you know, I, I happen to, it, it, it
depends on what you're doing, but I'll
share, like I use cloud code a lot.
If you use cloud code, it's, um, you know,
A lot of people think of it as vibe coding,
which it's certainly great for that or
creating apps and doing those things.
I don't really do a lot of that work myself.
Um, but to that point, Mike, I've actually
taken things like our entire curriculum.
If any of you, you do education and you
want to repurpose things and do
marketing or content or any and all of
those things.
Um, I'll take this company as an example
in Claude code, I've taken this entire
curriculum and Claude code, just like you
could do in cowork.
has created a file system of this
curriculum.
So it's all in PowerLabs, all our processes,
all our resources, what we teach you all.
And so I can literally go in there in a
prompt and be like, create an ad on lead
to sale, market to lead, all of these things,
or repurpose content, make a blog post,
make these things.
And it's literally a sentence and it can pull
any and everything that I sort of wanted
to work up.
So we do everything from webinars
social content to certain things like that.
And it's very simple.
Um, just like I'm sure it is in cowork.
I don't use cowork much.
It's, it's part of cloud code.
It's in there.
Um, but yeah, if that's helpful as well.
Yeah.
If anybody hasn't used cowork, it's pretty
new, but it's, I think the easiest way to
think of it is like intermediate between
cloud chat, cloud codes, kind of, if the chat
is beginner, cloud codes, intermediate, uh,
uh, cloud code is advanced and cowork.
is kind of intermediate.
But supposedly if you're not that great at
things, it's also better for security because
code doesn't really have the same
protection security wise, which I think is
one of the things I'm concerned about.
And if there's any advice on how to
manage that, when you start connecting, I
have not connected my email, but I've
connected some things to drive.
But I'm a little concerned about the
granularity and just like, I don't want,
full access to everything, especially when
you talk about agents where they can
start acting, not just reading.
And of course, probably everybody's
familiar with some of the nefarious
behavior of some of these AIs.
So I don't know, do you have any
suggestions related to using the different
tools and especially when we move away
from chat and granting access to our
information, how to manage that safely?
Yeah, I mean, so in terms of, co-work to
your point.
Yeah.
If people aren't using it, it's basically, you
know, beyond chat bots, it's on your
computer and it's about like managing,
organizing and creating files on your
computer.
In terms of security, it's a really good
question.
And it's kind of, the answer is kind of the
spectrum that you get with how people
think about AI.
And what I mean by that is I happen to do
cloud code to Mike's point.
So that actually connects to everything in
my computer.
So that has access to every single thing.
So some of you might hear that and get a
little uptight about it.
Others have a different view.
So I come from the view with AI is I believe
there's sort of two fundamental ways at
its simplest form, Mike.
There's two fundamental ways that we
can look at AI.
We can either say, I'm going to kind of use
it and I'm going to do that for my business
in this case.
And I'm going to use it as best as possible
while being worried about security.
I have taken the approach and a lot of
people have taken the approach of, I think
this is a world that is absolutely
inevitable.
And so I'm not going to put any blockers in
terms of
me reaching its full capabilities which
right now, which is access, right?
Whether you think at what we're sort of
teaching in the business world, or if you
want to understand what's going to be
possible in the personal efficiency world,
there's people who believe that we're
going to be cyborgs and our cell phones
will be connected to us.
And then there won't be bandwidth issues
with our brains anymore.
I mean, there's a lot of articles that you all
can read, and i'm sure we all have, uh,
thoughts on how sort of this plays out in.
20, 50 plus years from now.
But that's how I've looked at it.
I believe there is nothing that is going to
stop AI adoption.
I actually don't think it's possible.
And so I've chosen to sort of just embrace
that.
And the fact that there's nothing really on
my computer, my personal computer to
hide, if that helps anybody.
I understand that perspective.
pretty open to AI doing pretty much
everything.
But I've read a lot of experts that say you
really need to be careful.
I think something like Open Cloud or
Cloudbot is a good example.
Like Ethan Mollick just said, you should
not be installing that.
Basically because it has full access to
everything and it's unpredictable the way
it's going to behave or what it might do.
So I worry about code the same way, not
because just because I don't think security
is something that we should bypass based
on optimism about AI.
So I definitely think there should be some
structure around that.
Yeah, and nobody's wrong, right?
Like I said, there's really two ways to think
of this.
The set, if you all are not familiar with
OpenClaw that was formerly ClawedBot,
You're right.
And it's the same thing sort of with a lot of
the security settings if you're using
something like Cloud Code in the sense
that it's going to have access.
Again, it's strictly perspective because the
other side of the spectrum, OpenAI just
bought them.
And so, again, this is sort of like how you
look at things.
It's either sort of like, hey, I sort of put my
guardrails up or I believe you can say, I
think this is inevitable.
I think this is where the future of business
and the world in this case is going.
And so it's, you know, there's no right
answer.
I use clog code.
It certainly has access to everything I'm
doing on my computer.
But in no way do I not understand Mike's
stance or anybody else's who would say,
hey, you know what?
I'm not really ready to do that for a variety
of reasons of the what if type of dialogue
that you could have.
It's understandable.
Yeah.
The whole world of cyber reliability will
make your hair curl.
Yeah.
And again, I'm a very optimistic guy in the
sense that I truly believe that my stance
on AI is this is great.
I mean, this is great personally.
It's great for business.
I could go on this whole call of what I love
about it.
However, of any of the thoughts that all of
you have had, just like myself, of like what
could happen on the negative side, I think
it's like anything else that's ever been
around in human existence.
It will take an individual person to be able
to perhaps do some of those things.
I don't know that AI will start.
You know, all of the things that have been
fairly negative that I've seen on Reddit
and things like that, I think it's people
really starting to engineer prompts in very
specific ways.
Um, so again, it's, I happen to, I'm
embracing AI for its full capabilities, but
Mike zero resistance out of me or
probably anybody else here.
If you want to really, really still keep a lot
of security up for you personally.
Um, makes sense.
Easy question, Josh.
I'm wondering how long are we promised
access to the curriculum and what we're
using online with you guys?
So after it's done, it's two months.
And so you'll have access to the
community and the curriculum.
And the reason for that is it changes.
Like we constantly do cohorts.
And so you'll be able to log in, make sure
you're done.
And again, at the end of the course, it's
more about like, implementation, which I
know is why you're all here.
You don't want to just talk about doing
cool things to make your business more
efficient.
But we'll be there to make sure we
support you in any way that you need it.
Anybody else have any thoughts?
Um, you know, Pavlo, I know you're
possibly a little behind on curriculum and
things like that, but anything you're going
through right now, um, or anybody else,
um, wherever you're at in the curriculum
or assessments, whatever session, um,
you know, if you guys have any questions,
I'd be happy to help you out.
Hello to everyone.
I'll try to tell what I'm doing right now.
I'm literally behind because I'm starting
too late.
And I want to say I use a lot of transcribe
meetings internally.
We have 200 people in my factory and we
We make recordings of our meetings
one-to-one or meeting of our leaders.
For example, strategic session.
It can take maybe 10 days, all session.
And we use Notebook.LM.
We put together all transcribed notes.
And it's very helpful because we have our
knowledge and we can use all year.
If somebody forgets something, we always
use it.
Yeah.
So I want to use this master prompt, not
only for external calls and also with our
internal audio recordings, maybe some
meetings.
or one-to-one or retrospective between
our employees.
Yeah, that's great.
Yeah, we actually used Notion for a little
while, keeping our processes before stage
three for all our internal documentation,
knowledge and things like that.
But yeah, it sounds like your biggest
learning curve is the transcription part,
right?
Like the actual, you're taking our stuff and
having to translate it.
So hopefully that, I haven't had that
challenge, so hopefully that's sort of
coming out pretty legible for you and all of
your 200 people as you go through that.
It's kind of cool.
Also, I tried to play with SOP.
We are Lean factory.
We use Lean, I think, 10 years in high level.
And I love to make before and after
process So if we make SOP with master
prompt, we should before SOP make
improvement.
So we must clean waste from like lean
muda, eliminate waste.
So before SOP, we must change process
and make a new process clean.
And then we make SOP and I try with
cloud, make prompt for value stream
mapping, make improvements, and then I
make SOP.
It's very helpful.
And I think with master prompt, it will be
much more easy.
Yeah.
I'm glad to hear it.
And again, I know you're a little behind for
everybody.
He joined a bit after you all did, but yeah, I
mean, what you're doing, high level is
your, the sequence here is like you're,
you're documenting, you know, you, you
map and kind of capture your, your core
processes four levels deep.
Those are the SOPs.
Then you have, then you assess, right?
So you can kind of score against value
drivers or how owner dependent you are
in, in different areas and things like that.
Um, then you can sort of augment and
then systematize.
So the augments like AI can help you.
Cause it has context and then system
systematized would be just integrating it
with your current operating system or
some of the systems that you're already
using for your company.
Awesome.
Anybody else have anything that's come
up for them that they want to discuss?
Well, one thing I will say, if we don't have
any more questions is, um, you know, in,
in circle, you, you saw an example
yesterday of, of someone kind of going
through and saying, Hey, I was running
the assessment and sort of Claude
presented a scenario where he, he, I
believe he sort of had two different ways
that he could look at that.
And, you know, Midori had a, you know, a
good response to, to kind of answer that
with, and Midori, why don't you can, you
can tell them a little bit about that if you'd
like.
Thanks, Josh.
Yeah, so yesterday, I believe it was Matt,
had a issue pop up as he was working
through the delivery to success SOPs.
And that was that Claude sort of wanted
to ask some questions about whether a
boundary felt right about the assessment
that they just did and was proposing to
actually, instead of divide things up, keep
it all under one sort of solo practice
because of the nature of the business.
And so the question that was posed was,
does it make sense to do as Claude
suggests or does it make sense to do as
the original prompt suggests?
And at the end of the day, there's sort of
not, you know, a right answer.
One of the, you really have to sort of
decide what works for you.
in this case, Hayden and I were meeting
and so we were talking it through a little
bit.
And, you know, one of the benefits in this
particular case was that given the nature
of this person's business, it was actually
going to produce something that would be
highly specific to what they need and isn't
covered in the cohort.
And so that might actually be an
interesting exercise for Matt to go
through.
But to Matt's sort of conclusion to sort of
staying within the cohort so that we're all
sort of uniformly working through the
same material.
And, you know, we have the same kind of
what best looks like to continue to iterate
out once the cohort is done is also an
important piece.
Josh and I were also talking about it today
about how when this sort of scenario pops
up at this point, Claude has an awful lot of
information about your business.
And so it
it's a really good opportunity to actually
have a back and forth with Claude about,
you know, the pros and cons of going one
route versus the other.
So you can sort of sort out what would be
the best path for you.
I don't know if there's anything else you
want to add to that, Josh.
No, I mean, I guess just out of curiosity,
has anyone else experienced that where
potentially, because this has happened a
lot in the last cohort is Claude started to
make different suggestions.
Like, hey, I think this essentially like, hey,
this might be a good idea for you to
explore.
Doesn't seem like anybody maybe on the
call has dealt with that.
But to Midori's point, if you do, it is really
good with the context, like she said, to
unpack that.
Like, since you have all this context in
your master prompt project, you can say,
well, you know, tell me why that would
outweigh, let's say we're talking about a
go-to-market strategy.
It could be anything.
Tell me why that would be better than
what I was talking about for my go-to
market strategy and why you think this
give me like three pros and cons to this
and, and why it's better tied to my
strategic initiatives.
You know, having a back and forth
dialogue like that would be an example.
If Claude makes a suggestion, um, I do, uh,
this has happened to me for sure,
especially in, in go-to market strategies.
It's important to have the dialogue and
not just sort of like, oh, that's a really cool
plan.
I'll just go do that.
Especially if it's different than something
that you've done before.
It would be getting very, very clear on why
Claude would suggest that relative to
whatever you're already doing in your
operation.
Don, I see you have your hand raised.
Yeah, I have.
Very engaged in all this stuff.
You triggered a question here that I, a
little mystery.
I'm just checking on this co-work thing
that I worked with.
I was like suddenly wondering, how much
is co-work aware of all of our other
conversations that I did in the chat?
And it seems like it's somewhat tuned in.
What do you guys think?
I don't use co-work a whole lot myself.
I would suggest you just, like anything,
there's a bunch of stuff with AI these days.
I would just look at their privacy policy in
terms of service and understand their
security.
You know, you won't have the same
securities right now as you're going
through things, building your master
prompt, just using Claw in the project
form, like we talked about.
But however, if you're doing different
things, once you're
executing and everything like, you know,
for example, like I mentioned, I'm using
clog code for certain things that is, has
access to every single thing on my
computer.
Um, and it's, it's using the local storage on
my computer as well.
And there's a variety of different ways
that you can revise that.
So any and every tool that you use, I
would just encourage you to look up the
security settings.
But, uh, so cowork invites you to point it
at a folder.
So I made a folder, I dropped a few
documents in there and I wanted to
co-work to be aware of all of our
conversations on the chat side.
And so anyway, I don't know how hooked
up that is.
I did ask Claude not to do training on its,
you know, there was an option on there
you guys pointed out that where you said,
no, don't train the whole world on what
we're doing here.
Yeah.
I did just look up, by the way, so co-work
does not have unrestricted default access
to your entire computer.
It operates within a secure and sort of
virtualized sandbox environment.
But does it have access to all
conversations on the chat side?
That's what I'm wondering.
it should only be like accessing specific
files or folders.
You specifically grant permission to do so
because you do, as you know, it will
actually ask you permission for whatever
prompt that you put in or task in this case.
Okay.
So kind of like notebook lm you've faded
files.
It talks about those files.
Yeah.
Because you, you have to point co-work to
specific folders.
It can't access files outside of that scope.
So when you say like, if you said, go into
my Don work file and pull up, look
through all the invoices I've sent out and
find and pull the, you know, the highest
revenue ones over the last 12 months, it
will literally do that task for you.
That's awesome.
And put them in a new folder.
Um, but before you do that, there will be a
question to say, can I access this folder
specifically?
Okay.
And unfortunately, I won't access my
Google Drive, my virtual Google Drive.
I have to move files onto my C drive before
it can get access to it.
Kind of a pain in the butt.
Well, for co-work, yes.
I mean, if you're talking about your
master prompt for like your company,
that's exactly what it does.
Or if you store it on Google Drive, which a
lot of people do once it's finished, if they
use that for their company currently or
Microsoft or.
our stage three software, it's really, the
advice on that is store it where you
typically were operating, like whatever
you use, it's a little easier that way.
But we certainly can recommend if you
have questions about it.
And we cover that in the end, once the
master prompt is sort of finished, like,
hey, how do you store this, share this with
your team and all of those things.
But right now, currently we're, as you all
know, kind of going through each section
of your business to do the assessments.
Hi, everybody, by the way.
Hey, Matt.
I've been around.
Unfortunately, schedule-wise, I haven't
been able to make any live sessions, but
this has been a hell of a course so far, and
so thanks for all the work.
Thank you, my friend.
I appreciate that.
Well, no pressure, Matt, but you just
logged in, so wherever you're at, you can
share with everybody, or if you have
anything you'd like to unpack, we'd be
happy to help.
Of course, you can learn a lot from us, but
also these people have been going
through the program with you.
So it's just a kind of a open Q and a or
open dialogue.
Do you have a couple of questions?
Um, as far as where I'm at, I'm, I'm, I just
finished the fourth, uh, lesson and all of
the prompts and all of that.
And, um, and so I think the question I had,
cause this just came up is that at times
Claude gets a little, um,
Ambitious.
And so at one point he, you know, it was
putting together like all of the level one,
level two sops into one big document.
And I had just finished the video about
splitting that off.
And so i said hey hey whoa i don't want
one big document.
I want like multiples.
And I'm curious.
So what happened in this, I learned this
before and i'll tell you guys how i handle
it.
And then i'm curious on whether i'm doing
it the right way or if anybody else sees
this, but Oftentimes when I ask Claude or
Jim and I to do something like that, where
it's like, okay, you've created this
document, but really what I wanted was
these four, I would get errors in the
documents that it made.
And so what I started to do is after it
would produce that new document, I
would have it do an audit.
I would say, Hey, I want you to audit it
against the project files.
Tell me what you find and find it.
And then I would have it reproduce, you
know, and then I would have it,
you know, go from there at times that's
worked really well.
And then sometimes it feels like a going
down a rabbit hole where it's like, I get
errors.
It just kind of compounds.
So I'm curious, like how you guys handle
situations like that.
Didn't see it happen.
Yeah.
I mean myself, I mean, how I typically do it
when I create an SOP in this course
regard, like, so let's say you're going
through an assessment and I create a
level one SOP, for example, Um, I, I
personally have never used Claude, um, to
sort of, you know, go back on its own.
That's when I like it does the, the, the time
consuming part for me.
So I like to just go over the SOP or
whatever architect you end up producing.
That's what, where I spend my time.
Most of the questions in the back and
forth are pretty, or I'll say fairly
straightforward.
So when an SOP is created, I'm going to go
over it with my eyeballs and just say, Hey,
you know, change this part and then just
redo it.
And that's going to be the finalized
version.
So that could be one to potentially a lot of
iterations if Claude doesn't understand
some things about your company in that
regard.
But, you know, like anything, there's no
one way to do anything.
If you all have been in a similar experience
as Matt, you feel free to share how you've
kind of unpacked that for yourself if
helpful.
I do have a follow-up on that too that I'm
curious on because it kind of one leads
into the other is that one of the situations
I ran into was realizing as I went through
the process.
So I, for, I guess, for everybody's sake,
cause I haven't been on here before.
I, um, I'm the executive vice president for
a marketing agency, but I just launched a
consulting division business unit.
And that's really kind of where I'm gonna
be spending all my time going forward.
And I'm having to build it from scratch,
um, how we do strategic engagements,
differentiation, everything.
Um, and so in building those processes,
my original, you know, I had phases
essentially.
And what happened in doing the exercise
yesterday is that I realized that there
were some blueprint style sections that
were kind of in the wrong phase.
So kind of the same question as before,
but like when you iterate, like you guys
are all going through your business
processes or, or Josh Midori, What is the
ideal way to go back and iterate on that
stuff?
I can tell you what I did.
And I was in the success to delivery chat.
And when I was like, oh, I need to do this.
And I asked it, I was like, hey, what would
be the best way to go about this?
And it basically created a guide.
And then I went and started a new chat.
I uploaded the guide, uploaded all of the
documents in the previous iteration.
And, and then it reproduced those
documents.
And so i just basically went through it that
way.
Is that what everybody else is doing when
you're iterating like that or have
something comes up where it kind of
changes your SOPs?
Yeah.
And certainly anybody else can answer.
I would say yes.
Um, again, I, I think that as you're going
through any of these, the, the reason the
prompts are structured the way that they
are, Matt, why, why there's a conversation
is because it it starts to let you know
what, Claude doesn't understand about
your business.
And so for you, if you're focusing on the
consultating processes from scratch
outside of your marketing agency, there's
probably a little bit more that you will
have to do in that regard, just because
we've had people do the exact same thing.
And I haven't done it from like starting
from scratch business, but I would think
that Claude is very optimistic and it
probably
gives very grandiose plans and things that
sound good, especially if this is truly
starting from scratch.
And so that's what I remind everybody.
You know, there's a lot of solopreneur to
like 10 person companies here that, that
last part of the third SOP, we're a small
team, you know, and power lab is about
10 people.
So, you know, some of the plans that get
spit out that last part of the, the SOP
process of like, is this over engineered for
a team my size or, Is this completely
over-engineered knowing that I'm starting
this process from scratch and just having
that kind of iterative process, but I don't
think you're doing anything wrong by any
means.
I appreciate that.
I had, I had a, yeah, let's say a similar issue
in the same cohort, sorry, in the same
part.
I think it's four, number four.
I discussed that with Hayden.
And my solution at the end was going
back to two steps before, reiterate it
again, and create a new chat doing the
same work.
And while doing that, I detected I might
forgot to add one chat output, so an
empty file.
the project as an artifact.
And therefore, he lost traction and
created then strange proposals for the
blueprints.
Totally wrong.
And yeah, it's an assumption because I
cannot remember because it's so
overwhelming.
I don't know where I stepped out of the
procedure.
Anyway, it is sometimes worse to step one
step back and then going to forward, let's
say.
Yeah, that's my experience.
I've definitely experienced before this
course, the grandiosity for sure.
My phase zero of, you know, five phase
approach to doing a strategic
engagement.
I work specifically in tourism.
So I work with destination marketing
organizations and
It was like 28 pages for phase zero.
Yeah.
And Matt, why we certainly appreciate
that because obviously if you were a, a
larger mature organization, um, that, that
is awesome.
But that again, it's that key part of, I do
this a lot, you know, there's, there's
constant iterations, right?
Like even internally, since it's your call,
Matt, I'll tell you, you know, as, as a
leadership team here with our master
prompt, you know, we, we built it.
And we had our core one, but then
different people of the leadership team
own different actual like lead to sale or
market to lead wherever you are the
leader at.
And we thought we were going to redo the
assessment quarterly.
That was the idea that in our head, but
the truth is, is it, it ends up happening a
lot sooner than that.
It even for the variety of reason, if like,
think about for all of you can relate to in
the simplest form, whatever assessment
they're talking about delivery to success,
but
Let's say someone leaves someone in
sales, someone in marketing, someone in
your operation leaves.
That's a big part that I, you know, iterate
like, Hey, this person left, we hired a new
person or this person left in the
meantime, I am filling the gap or this
person is now filling the gap.
How can we streamline with their
responsibilities, ABC, along with D E and F
to make sure that they're not
overwhelmed.
I mean, there's the editor of process is
great.
Because above anything, you're getting
thought leadership from AI on top of
speed, efficiency, quality of output,
because it has the business brain.
So the iterative process will never stop.
And just like Benny's point, like if you
forget to add an artifact to your master
prompt or you end up going back by the
end of this, you might say something
drastically changed in my marketing
process or my sales or
you know, delivery to success.
But if you have account managers in
Matt's case, if he's an agency or what,
everyone has a lot of different types of
businesses, but you could go back, reopen
the chat from, and from this last produced
artifact, I'd like you to, you know, take it
wherever you want to go from there.
And then to Matt's point, you're looking at
the output and then you may take that
and save it over your, you know, delivery
to success assessment, just to make sure
things are, up to date.
I, um, well, my last two things is I know
we're at time.
Um, one, are, are you guys, this might be a
dumb question.
Are you guys saving the HTML files into
your projects or is that only for stage
three?
That's a good question.
I had the same.
Yeah.
He had the same.
I mean, you, you can absolutely do it,
Benny.
I think you were, I think you were asking,
specifically about your SOP.
So the, an SOP artifact is just a markdown
file, but in an HTML file specifically, you
can certainly put it in your master
prompt.
Um, it becomes a little more convenient in
stage three map, just because when you
copy you literally, instead of like, I'm not
sure how you're adding it to your master
prompt.
You saw the different ways, but for the
HTML, when you put it in stage three, it
immediately populates like the visual
element, which is super helpful.
And really what you won't see in Claude,
unless you're sort of looking into the
artifact itself, opposed to like in the
master prompt.
So does that answer your question?
No, it totally does.
And then another project file question is
that eventually what I need to do will be
to have this instance guide me with how
to set up things like Asana, because that's
what we'll do for project management
within the environment that I'm in.
When you guys are doing that, do you
suggest, I mean, is there enough built in
baked in knowledge for Claude to handle
instructions?
Because what I've run into in the past is
that sometimes it'll tell you to do all these
things and it's, you know, either
hallucinating or it's using an old version or
whatever.
So do you guys typically like go and
download some big manual for like Asana
or whatever, and then put that in the
project files?
Is that good idea, bad idea?
No, I think it's a good question.
How I've handled this is the good news is
with the open API, things can pretty much
integrate directly.
Now, an easy way, a lot of people use
Zapier for a variety of reasons.
It's cheap.
At this point, it kind of integrates with
everything.
And at worst case,
whatever system like Asana or let's say
you use kind of a rare system, I'm pretty
confident that it'll integrate with Zapier.
And like one thing that I've figured out
through Claude is like sometimes things
don't directly integrate, but in just having
a dialogue with Claude, Matt, like
anything will zap to a Google Sheet and
Google Sheet will go to anything.
So sometimes I've just added a step like,
hey, this isn't in automation or workflow
in this scenario.
But I absolutely start just like you said,
like if I said, hey, I use Asana as my project
management tool in my company blank or
like I'm wanting to use it for my new
consulting, however you're going about
this.
This is the current technology that I have.
I have nothing but a Google Drive and I
just signed up for Asana.
This is the workflow and all of these
different things.
You could kind of unpack that.
And I'm looking to integrate this directly.
Could you give me an overview framework
of exactly what that would look like from
a technical standpoint?
A lot of times it will give you is like, well,
you're going to need a connector to
connect this and you could use Zapier or
different other web hooks and things.
Or like if it's open API, like it just connects
here and it'll tell you where to get that in
Asana, for example.
right?
It'll go to settings and this is where you
get your open API webhook.
So it does pretty good.
I also will say like, I'm not a developer, like
deep.
There's a lot of things that are connected
open API that you will have, you will need
like some level of technical prowess.
But for anybody of just saying like, hey,
how would, whether it's a workflow or an
automation or anything that you're
looking to achieve from a technical
standpoint, Claude, you'd be surprised.
Claude's pretty good at least giving you
the foundational overview of what that's
going to look like.
If it's too complicated, of course, you
might have to inquire someone else to set
it up.
I guess my tip, I don't know if this is a tip
or not, but one thing that I would suggest
people experimenting with that's been
very helpful to me, something I was
actually doing before I joined the course, I
started this like last fall, was to create
what I call a master profile.
Because one of the things that I deal with
is having ADHD.
And so when you travel, like I do a
hundred and something days a year and
have different things going on, like ADHD
is a real pain in the butt.
And so what I ended up doing was
essentially I started off with like a voice
dump is what I call it.
So I went for a walk for like an hour and
just talked.
I uploaded that as a starting spot.
And then had it kind of get a base of who I
was.
And then I essentially, you know, said,
hey, I have ADHD.
And, you know, like everybody else that
has it, you know, you go to the doctor and
they say, yep, you got it after like five
questions.
And here's some Adderall and pat you on
the back and off you go.
And that's great for about a month until
you realize that like, it's really not that
magical after about that long.
And so I had to do a much longer
assessment, which if you have ADHD, you
would understand that like, being given a
hundred question assessment is like
climbing mount Everest, but i did it
through voice, which made it a lot easier.
So I was basically transcribing the notes in
otter and then just uploading those
dialogues, which also had the benefit of
helping it further understand my
personality.
And then i did basically every major
personality or other assessment,
everything from the colby to what is it the
the briar i can't remember, but anyway,
Yep.
I did about 10 of those.
I think it cost me, I think I ended up
spending about $200 total and uploaded
all those assessments.
I did.
I uploaded enough material on the
chronotype book to do a chronotype
assessment.
And so what it did for me was that it
created a master profile that said, this is
who Matt is.
This is when he does his best work.
This is where he's weak.
And one of the things that's really come
out in this course for me is that as I've
gone through this, it's repeatedly
reminded me in things like the blueprints
where I'm very weak in the middle phase.
So I'm big on wonder and invention and
those sorts of things.
So zero to 25, I'm really good.
And then when I'm under a deadline, 75 to
100% of a project and I'm under stress,
then I can put out 150% and get it done.
It's in the middle where things go to die
with me.
So where I've really found it very helpful,
and this includes how I've had to modify
things like the second brain from Tiago, is
making it work for me and my particular
setup of my mental setup.
So even like the tools I use, my tech stack
that I use, and it's constantly reminding
me, yeah, that sounds great, but you're
never going to stick with that.
It sounds awesome, but you're never
going to do that.
And it also helps me in terms of like, now
with this, what we've been doing and
having those processes, um, I've been
playing with it.
And what I found it to be really useful is
that like, because it understands the
processes down to the nth degree, I can
actually have it, schedule it out on my
calendar.
And because it understands me and it
understands the work and understands
the time involved to do the work because
of this class, it's actually been successful
in blocking out time.
That's appropriate, like for a full project,
essentially.
over the course of weeks to get it done.
And that's a godsend for me, but I, I, any
case, I I'm happy to share if people are
interested, I'm happy to post kind of what
my methodology was to create that.
It's far less sophisticated than what we're
doing here, but it has, I did load it into the
empower project.
Yeah.
And I think it has been very, very helpful
as I've gone through this process.
It's really been, it's a powerful
combination.
So that was, I guess that's my, my offering
to the group.
And again, if there's interest, I'll post it in
the discussion about how I went about it.
Yeah, man.
Thank you for sharing.
And yeah, please post.
I know everyone's asking, but someone
will for sure get value from that.
So I would encourage you to post it.
And by the way, like just on that, like
there's been so many people who have
done different versions of this.
I know internally,
Matt, we've all taken at Empower Labs,
we've taken all the assessments, Colby,
Cantor, Pathfinder, you name it, we've
taken it.
And I'm the kind of guy personally, like I
do those just to do them.
I'm like, I'll do the assessment, I'll get the
results.
And so I have found funny ways to take
the information of everyone on the
leadership team and build a project with
all of the outputs of everyone there.
For example, like when conflict comes up,
Um, when they're like leadership does not
agree when there is friction points, how
we make decisions, how we communicate,
right?
All of those things are, are, are measured
in full transparency.
I didn't look at any of the results.
I did, however, put all of our results in a
cloud project.
And so if I have to talk to a specific person
who all of these assessments have, have,
uh, literally three full assessments, um, I
will say I'm going to go with this intention
in mind.
I will use that.
We've had people build their own master
prompts for their personal health.
You know, it's a lot of cool things people
have shared.
And just like Matt, by the way, I'll sort of
leave you all with this.
We all do this internally is what Matt said.
And you can add this to your master
prompt, especially as you start using it
post cohort is personal preferences.
So the easiest way to explain this is in the
assessment form is we all have strengths
and weaknesses, right?
So Matt can mention like, Hey, I have
ADHD.
So like in his personal preferences, like
there's, there's, here's are my strengths
and my personal preferences.
These are my strengths.
These are my weaknesses.
And the key point that might be helpful
for you, Matt, if you don't have this, is
this, these are some key things that could
be bullet points of how I want
this AI to help me on a daily, weekly,
monthly, quarterly, yearly basis.
So that's a little bit of a step up because
it's your master prompt, all the business
stuff, but it's literally saying like, hey, I
struggle with ADHD.
So if I'm going down a rabbit hole, I want
to make sure I'm making this up.
But like if I'm an hour and a half in an
assessment because of my ADHD, I want
you to tie back the project to my strategic
initiatives to make sure I'm not going
down an unnecessarily, you know, rabbit
hole in a make-believe example.
But Hayden has different sort of pros,
cons, and what he uses AI for.
The easiest way for business owners is use
AI to do the things that you hate doing.
That's the easy sort of like, this is things I
just hate doing.
And other times I get fulfillment and all of
those things.
So Sebastian, he just signed off, but he put
it, the sugar mill we're implementing
step-by-step
the learnings from the cohort.
Claude is currently used to solve complex
situations with great success.
At this time, we apply it to develop the
strategy for implementing the IEC 62402
standard for, uh, obsolescence
management.
Um, it is possible and it works.
Consider that we are a large agricultural
and industrial enterprise.
Um, cool.
Yeah.
And you know what?
I'll send you, um, I'll post a case study on
these guys.
Um, You know, he's, um, Sebastian's been
pretty silent, but we have an amazing case
study that I'm going to post in the group
after this, just for you all to see, cause it's
a sugar mill in Guatemala and they, um,
they solved, uh, the definition of a
complex problem, um, with sort of using
our processes and they saved, you know,
hundreds of thousands, if not millions of
dollars in doing so, which, which teaching
the editor of process that we all kind of
unpacked on today's call.
So.
Matt, please do post any and all stuff like
that.
That will be valuable for people for sure.
I'm glad that you joined the call, my
friend.
Hope to see you on the next one.
And if anybody needs anything as it comes
up, please lean on Circle.
We will be here to support you.
Otherwise, we will see you Monday on the
next call.
Thanks, everyone.
Have a good one.
Thank you.
Thanks.